

JULIO MIRANDOLA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

◆ BAURU, BRAZIL

◆ 18998188158

• DETAILS •

Bauru Brazil 18998188158 julionm60@gmail.com

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

CodePen

GitHub

LeetCode

• SKILLS •

React

Laravel

Angular

Spring

CSS3

Git

• LANGUAGES •

English

Portuguese

• HOBBIES •

I like to read a lot, from technical books like Clean Code and Clean Architecture to science fiction books. CSS is for me one of the biggest charmings of front-end development, thus I really like to test it and learn new things I can do with it.

PROFILE

I've worked with many different technologies through out my entire career. From Angular to React, from Spring to Laravel, from Front-end Developer to Full Stack, working with infrastructure and offering client support. In all these distinguished scenarios I had opportunities to learn, try, fail, succeed and in the end, what matters most, is all the knowledge gained in this never ending pursue for delivering the best solution I can for a problem you have.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Developer at Up Outsourcing, Bauru

April 2022 — Present

I worked as a Full Stack Developer in a range of distinguished projects. I had experience working with older versions of PHP and with other newer frameworks, such as Symphony and Laravel. With front-end I had experience with jQuery and React, using Redux for state management.

For styling we used Tailwind, Bootstrap and Styled Components.

Together with the american customers I developed my english so we could have a clean and clear communication with each other.

Full Stack Developer at ViewB, Bauru

June 2018 — April 2022

Worked as a Full Stack Developer using Angular and Spring, creating solutions for the Analytics platform.

I worked with customer support and helped other teams to solve problems related to our product.

I helped on the server maintenance using Nginx and Tomcat to deploy our Spring application.

EDUCATION

Técnico em Informática, Colégio Técnico Industrial - Isaac Portal Roldan, Bauru February 2016 — December 2018

Here I got my certificate in IT and learned the basics of computer programming during college. While there, I created projects using C and PHP with HTML/CSS/JS for web development. For the final project I gathered with some friends to create a project using Unity and Blender to help students learn some biology concepts.

COURSES

CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python, HarvardX March 2024 — April 2024